So we've talked about now an exercise that can help us think about syntax how we organize our sentences
所以我们现在讨论了一个练习，它可以帮助我们思考句法我们如何组织我们的句子
how we can fit words that we know together into a coherent story.
我们如何将我们知道的单词组合成一个连贯的故事。
Now this exercise the simplification exercise is all about forcing ourselves to find the simple way
现在这个练习简化练习就是强迫自己找到简单的方法
to explain something.
解释某事。
In fact much of natural English especially natural spoken English is quite simple.
事实上，自然英语尤其是自然口语的大部分内容都非常简单。
People often speak very simply.
人们常常说得很简单。
So when you look at something that's written down and you say Wow it's very long and complicated it
所以当你看到写下来的东西时，你会说哇，它很长而且很复杂
is certainly possible and even likely that that can be actually said in a much simpler way.
这当然是可能的，甚至可能实际上可以用一种更简单的方式来表达。
We're going to do that now.
我们现在就这样做。
OK.
好的。
Now the one we're going to look at is not actually very good but you could also do this for literature
现在我们要看的那个实际上不是很好，但你也可以为文学做这个
for example if you read a page of a book that's kind of complicated.
例如，如果您阅读一本有些复杂的书。
You can take that paragraph from that book and simplify it boil it down.
您可以从那本书中提取该段落并将其简化。
We often when we talk about simplifying things we talk about boiling it down to its simplest form.
当我们谈论简化事物时，我们经常谈论将其简化为最简单的形式。
So let's play around with this.
所以让我们玩这个。
And this is really play.
这真的是玩。
I consider this to be play.
我认为这是玩。
The more you can play with English and play with language the more comfortable that you'll be.
你玩英语和玩语言的次数越多，你就会越舒服。
And then you're going to be more creative when you want to express your ideas and speak.
当你想表达你的想法和说话时，你会更有创造力。
You're going to be able to express yourself creatively simply and clearly.
你将能够简单而清晰地创造性地表达自己。
OK.
好的。
So it was Christmas I spent the day with my family.
所以那是圣诞节，我和家人一起度过了这一天。
We opened presence together and made a big meal.
我们一起打开存在感，做了一顿丰盛的饭菜。
The meal was delicious.
这顿饭很好吃。
We had a great day together.
我们一起度过了美好的一天。
Christmas is my favorite holiday.
圣诞节是我最喜欢的节日。
So this is filled with a lot of redundant language.
所以这里充满了很多多余的语言。
Something is redundant.
有些东西是多余的。
That means it's really doesn't need to be said.
这意味着它真的不需要说。
OK.
好的。
So how do we eat a big meal.
那么我们如何吃一顿大餐。
The meal was delicious.
这顿饭很好吃。
OK we said meal twice.
好的，我们说了两次饭。
That's not so good.
那不是很好。
Christmas is my favorite holiday.
圣诞节是我最喜欢的节日。
Well if we're talking about how great Christmas is do we need to say that it's our favorite.
好吧，如果我们谈论圣诞节有多棒，我们是否需要说它是我们的最爱。
OK.
好的。
I spent the day with my family.
我和家人一起度过了这一天。
We opened presents together and had a big meal.
我们一起打开礼物，吃了一顿大餐。
It just sounds a little weird because the sentences are maybe too short.
这听起来有点奇怪，因为句子可能太短了。
The syntax is not great.
语法不是很好。
And there's a bit of repetition in words.
并且有一些重复的文字。
A bit of redundancy so stop the lesson here.
有点冗余，所以在这里停止课程。
Try your own try to try three different ones and see what you can come up with.
尝试你自己的尝试，尝试三种不同的，看看你能想出什么。
I'm going to try to variations to simplifications of the original text and see how close your eyes are
我将尝试对原文进行简化，看看你的眼睛有多近
to mine if they're not like mine.
如果他们不像我的，那就去我的。
That's totally ok.
这完全没问题。
There are many ways to do this.
有很多方法可以做到这一点。
Just see how well you can do it and then come back.
看看你能做到多好，然后再回来。
All right here we go.
好吧，我们走吧。
My first one.
我的第一个。
Let's see.
让我们来看看。
My family my family and I had a great time.
我的家人我的家人和我度过了愉快的时光。
Opening presents together on Christmas after a big delicious meal.
一顿丰盛的美味大餐后，在圣诞节一起打开礼物。
Wow you've said pretty much everything there.
哇，你已经说了几乎所有的东西。
My family and I had a great time.
我和我的家人玩得很开心。
Opening presents together on Christmas after a big delicious meal.
一顿丰盛的美味大餐后，在圣诞节一起打开礼物。
One sentence and we've said pretty much everything that's been said here.
一句话，我们已经说了几乎这里所说的一切。
And so we've removed a lot of the redundancy and it's very clear even though it's a lot simpler I would
所以我们已经删除了很多冗余，这很清楚，即使它更简单我会
say this is way better than the original.
说这比原版好多了最终。
Way way better.
好多了
OK then we could add maybe four four syntax.
好的，那么我们可以添加四个四个语法。
We can add one sentence.
我们可以加一句。
It's my favorite holiday.
这是我最喜欢的节日。
Christmas is my favorite holiday.
圣诞节是我最喜欢的节日。
So you have this very long sentence that says everything we want to say and then it's my favorite holiday.
所以你有一个很长的句子，说出了我们想说的一切，然后这是我最喜欢的假期。
A very simple sentence to give us some variation in our sentence style.
一个非常简单的句子，让我们的句子风格有所变化。
And if it's not there I think it's OK because we can kind of get a feeling that it's it's your favorite
如果它不在那里，我认为没关系，因为我们可以感觉到它是你最喜欢的
holiday.
假期。
It's actually not my favorite holiday by the way my favorite holiday is a very silly holiday that my
实际上，这不是我最喜欢的假期，因为我最喜欢的假期是一个非常愚蠢的假期，我
family and I invented which we call Hanks giving.
我和家人发明了我们称之为汉克斯捐赠的东西。
I just write that down.
我只是把它写下来。
It's a ridiculous thing.
这是一件可笑的事情。
We invented it.
我们发明了它。
It's called Hanks giving not Thanksgiving.
这叫汉克斯送礼而不是感恩节。
So there's an American holiday called Thanksgiving.
所以美国有个节日叫感恩节。
Well we celebrate one called Hanks giving.
好吧，我们庆祝一个叫做汉克斯的捐赠。
And if you know there's a famous actor his name is Tom Hanks.
如果你知道有一个著名的演员他的名字是汤姆汉克斯。
So on Hanks giving.
所以关于汉克斯的捐赠。
We get our friends together my family and I.
我们让我的家人和我的朋友聚在一起。
And we watch Tom Hanks movies.
我们看汤姆汉克斯的电影。
We play games Tom Hanks related games.
我们玩汤姆汉克斯相关的游戏。
We have trivia.
我们有琐事。
It's very weird.
这很奇怪。
It's very strange but we have a lot of fun.
这很奇怪，但我们玩得很开心。
It's quite interesting.
这很有趣。
Hanks giving something that only my family does it's not normal for sure.
汉克斯给的东西只有我的家人才会这样做，这肯定是不正常的。
OK.
好的。
So let's try one more of these and see if we can do another interesting variation variation.
因此，让我们再尝试其中一个，看看我们是否可以做另一个有趣的变化变化。
OK here we go.
好的，我们开始吧。
I spent I spent I spent this Christmas with my family and we'll just make that a simple sentence.
我度过了这个圣诞节，我和家人一起度过了，我们只是简单地说一句。
I don't want to say that long sentence equals good sentence.
我不想说长句等于好句。
That's not true.
这不是真的。
So you can have short sentences long sentences they can all be good sentences after a huge tasty meal.
所以你可以有短句长句，它们都可以是一顿丰盛的大餐后的好句子。
We all had a great time opening presence together.
我们一起度过了愉快的时光。
So now this one is a bit different because the sentences are about the same length but I would say it's
所以现在这个有点不同，因为句子的长度差不多，但我想说的是
no better or worse than the other one the first one we did.
没有比我们第一个做的更好或更差。
Now where could we put.
现在我们可以放在哪里。
It's my favorite holiday.
这是我最喜欢的节日。
If we want to put that in so we could put my favorite holiday at the end but we could also use which
如果我们想把它放进去，我们可以把我最喜欢的假期放在最后，但我们也可以用 which
I spent this Christmas comma which is my favorite holiday comma with my family.
我度过了这个圣诞逗号，这是我和家人最喜欢的节日逗号。
We could do that.
我们可以这样做。
That is something that you can do to add information to a sentence and it's really really useful.
这是您可以为句子添加信息的方法，它真的非常有用。
You can do it with people.
你可以和人一起做。
You can do it with things.
你可以用东西来做。
If it's a thing then usually you use which if it's a person you'll use who.
如果它是一个东西，那么通常你会使用 which 如果它是一个人，你会使用 who。
I'll just give you a very quick example of how to do that just so you know so that you can use it in
我将给你一个非常简单的例子来说明如何做到这一点，这样你就知道了，这样你就可以在
the future.
未来。
Let's make two short sentences.
让我们写两个简短的句子。
My uncle is a doctor.
我的叔叔是一名医生。
My uncle lives in Canada.
我叔叔住在加拿大。
OK.
好的。
To have two sentences this and this.
有两个句子this和this。
These two are the same.
这两个是一样的。
So we don't want to say both of those we can replace this with who or which person my uncle.
所以我们不想说这两个我们可以用我叔叔的谁或哪个人来代替。
So we should say who not which.
所以我们应该说谁不是哪个。
OK.
好的。
So here's what we do.
所以这就是我们要做的。
We take this one and we put it right there and then we add comma Hu comma or comma which comma very
我们拿这个，我们把它放在那里，然后我们添加逗号 Hu comma or comma which comma very
simple we could do it the other way to my uncle comma who is a doctor comma can if it's a thing we would
很简单，我们可以对我的叔叔逗号做其他方式，他是一名医生，如果这是我们愿意的事情，逗号可以
just say which there is my favorite holiday lives in Canada we change nothing about this sentence or
只要说出我最喜欢的加拿大假期生活我们对这句话没有任何改变或
this sentence we just take this sentence and into the other sentence using who or which if it's a thing
这句话我们只是把这句话和另一个句子使用 who or which if it's a thing
we could go the other way we could say my uncle who lives in Canada is a doctor this is so easy.
我们可以换一种方式，我们可以说我住在加拿大的叔叔是一名医生，这很容易。
So whenever you want to add information you can use this general grammar structure it allows you to
因此，每当您想添加信息时，您都可以使用这个通用语法结构，它允许您
put in things about a person or a thing in a way which really you don't have to think much about and
把关于一个人或一件事的事情以一种你真的不需要考虑太多的方式放进去，
when when should we put lives in Canada.
我们什么时候应该在加拿大生活。
Inside is a doctor.
里面是医生。
When should we do that instead of the other way.
我们什么时候应该这样做而不是其他方式。
Well I would say the main sentence is probably more important.
好吧，我想说主句可能更重要。
So my Cole lives in Canada is probably the most important thing we want to say.
所以我的科尔住在加拿大可能是我们想说的最重要的事情。
My uncle who is a doctor.
我叔叔是医生。
That's just extra information so I usually put the extra information inside the two commas.
这只是额外的信息，所以我通常将额外的信息放在两个逗号内。
It's called a comma.
它被称为逗号。
By the way a do you put the extra information there and then the main sentence is usually the more important
顺便说一句，您是否将额外信息放在那里，然后主要句子通常更重要
thing.
事物。
So these two exercises completing sentences by taking out key words from an article and then making
所以这两个练习通过从文章中取出关键词然后造句来完成句子
a story stitching them together and then simplifying a paragraph from an article or a novel or whatever
一个故事将它们拼接在一起，然后简化文章或小说或其他任何内容中的一段
and doing several simplified variations of that.
并做了几个简化的变体。
These are two powerful ways to get you to think more creatively in English and the more you do it the
这是让你用英语更有创意地思考的两种有效方法，而且你做得越多，
more powerful you're going to feel when you get into a situation you need to express yourself.
当您进入需要表达自己的情况时，您会感到更强大。
You're going to be able to put your words together a little bit more easily and that's going to allow
你将能够更容易地把你的话放在一起，这将允许
you to come across or speak more naturally you'll find your words more easily and you'll be able to
你会遇到或说话更自然你会更容易找到你的话，你将能够
stick them together without really thinking about it.
不假思索地把它们粘在一起。
If you practice this enough practice is extremely important.
如果你练习这个足够的练习是非常重要的。
You've got knowledge but you also need to practice it you've got to build the right habits.
你有知识，但你也需要练习它，你必须养成正确的习惯。
Gotta get comfortable in English you've got to do exercises.
得让英语舒服，你必须做练习。
So for an assignment.
所以为了一个任务。
Here are a couple of examples of very very short words that you can fit together into a sentence or
这里有几个非常短的单词示例，您可以将它们组合成一个句子或
a couple sentences.
几句话。
Very simple.
很简单。
OK.
好的。
Now once you've done these and you feel like it's pretty easy go a step further get an article from
现在，一旦你完成了这些，你会觉得这很容易，再往前走一步，从
the newspaper or a book or whatever and do the exercises that we learned in this lesson do them several
报纸或书或其他任何东西，然后做我们在本课中学到的练习，做几个
times when you choose one to do for simplification try 10 variations if you can.
当您选择一种进行简化时，如果可以，请尝试 10 种变体。
I want to emphasize it's very important to play play and having fun with it making it funny right.
我想强调玩游戏并从中获得乐趣非常重要，让它变得有趣。
Doing it a little differently.
做的有点不同。
Changing the style especially for the second one is really really important.
改变风格，尤其是第二种风格，真的很重要。
English can be actually a lot of fun if you jump in and swim around.
如果你跳进去游泳，英语实际上会很有趣。
So go practice.
所以去练习吧。
Good luck.
祝你好运。